Adam Haviv

ashaviv27@gmail.com

L 050-818-1126

github.com/ashvv1

In linkedin.com/in/adam-haviv-84bb17225/

https://www.adamhaviv.com

Profile

More than two years' experience working on professional and personal projects. Fast learning and initiative-taking autodidact with English as a first language.

Has experience in planning, prototyping, and developing a product from the ground up. Very passionate about learning and creating. Looking for a Full Stack, Front End or Back End Developer position which will allow me to utilize my relevant experience as well as grow as a developer.

Technical Knowledge/Experience

- Databases: MongoDB, Firestore, mySOL Cloud: AWS (EC2), Firebase, Mongo Atlas .
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Back-End: Node.JS, Express, PHP React.js, Next.js, jQuery, Svelte
- DevOps/Workflow: Docker, GitHub, Jira, Jenkins, EC2, ECR, Netlify, Heroku

Web3: Solidity, Web3 Integrations

Testing: Jenkins, Mocha

Professional Experience

Software Developer, Cambium LTD, April 2023 - Present

 Developing a wide variety of projects including automation and custom websites as part of a team or individually.

*Was previously in charge of project coordination and development of the product of a foreign client. Soft Skills: Flexibility. Willingness to learn new technologies from my peers, problem solving. Technologies: Typescript, React, Syelte, PHP, HTML, SCSS, MUI, Zustand

FullStack Developer(Intern), Minerva XR, August 2022 - April 2023

. Developing a wide variety of projects including automation and custom websites as part of a team or individually.

*Was previously in charge of project coordination and development of the product of a foreign client. Soft Skills: Flexibility, Willingness to learn new technologies from my peers, problem solving. Technologies: Firestore/Firebase, React.is, Node.is

Python Insructor, Cambium LTD, October 2022 - June 2023

 Teaching 10th graders Python while following a strict syllabus intended to prepare students for Army service in cyber units.

Soft Skills: Relaying complicated concepts in a simplified manner to high schoolstudents while developing their coding and problem-solving skills.

Education

SV College, January 2022 - June 2022

FullStack Development Program

Fullstack Development Program

Focus on MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node)

CodeCademy, October 2021 - Janury 2022 Online FullStack Course

Certificate of completion (Front-End Development)

Certificate of completion (JavaScript)

Languages

· Hebrew - Fluent

English - Native